<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>San Francisco Digital Services</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on San Francisco Digital Services</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Request for Proposals: Racial Equity Facilitation and Consultancy Support</title>
      <link>/rfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 14:01:51 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rfp/</guid>
      <description> Request for Proposals  Racial Equity Facilitation and Consultancy Support Digital Services is seeking one qualified supplier to provide racial equity facilitation and consultancy support for the City.
Last updated: November 3, 2021
Budget $64,500
 Timeline    Proposal Phase Tentative Date     Proposal issued by the City November 2, 2021   Deadline for Questions November 15, 2021   Deadline to submit Proposals&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; November 23, 2021   Notice of Intent to Award January 14, 2022     Responses to Questions  Responses to questions  RFP Links  RFP for Racial Equity Facilitation and Consultancy Support  Attachment 1: City’s Proposed Terms Attachment 2: Proposer Questionnaire and References Attachment 3-5: CMD Forms Attachment 6: Price Proposal Template Attachment 7: First Source Hiring Form Attachment 8: HCAO and MCO Declaration Forms    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/joinus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/joinus/</guid>
      <description> Interested in updates?   If you’d like to hear about future job opportunities and other updates, join our mailing list:
 Subscribe    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/ourwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ourwork/</guid>
      <description>San Francisco Digital Services Making Services For Everyone  Read the Full Report (PDF) --  About -- San Francisco Digital Services works with other City departments to improve public services. We use technology to make it easier for people to get things done.
We&#39;re working on critical issues like affordable housing, small businesses, legal aid for immigrants, and more. Our team is also rebuilding the city’s website from the ground up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/sfgov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sfgov/</guid>
      <description>A single website for San Franciscans San Francisco Digital Services Strategy --  Read the Full Report (PDF) --   About -- We’re building a new website for San Francisco.
Right now, we have 210 websites across the City with over 300,000 pages. But getting services from the City is frequently difficult and confusing. With so much information, residents don’t know which pages to trust. They might have to visit multiple sites to accomplish a task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/strategy/</guid>
      <description>Serving you better San Francisco Digital Services Strategy  Read the Full Report (PDF) --  About -- Imagine a city where a teenager in the Bayview can search for a summer internship from his cell phone, allowing him to gain valuable job training for a future career. Or a family in the Mission can apply for health insurance from a computer at their local library. Or where an aspiring café owner can apply for and track every permit for her business from her home office.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
